{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Latin is not ___ language.",
      "a": "live",
      "b": "alive",
      "c": "an alive",
      "d": "a living",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- a living language",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "There is _________ about Mr Brown, my teacher.",
      "a": "anything noble",
      "b": "noble something",
      "c": "something noble",
      "d": "noble anything",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Something + adjective",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Miss Kate is ___ her mother in many respects.",
      "a": "alike",
      "b": "similar",
      "c": "like with",
      "d": "like",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Be like somebody\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Don't eat too ___ sugar lest it should do you harm.",
      "a": "much",
      "b": "a little",
      "c": "many",
      "d": "few",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Much + uncountable nouns",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "She has failed this time, but there is still ___ hope.",
      "a": "few",
      "b": "a few",
      "c": "little",
      "d": "a little",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- A little + uncountable nouns",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "We should be polite to ___.",
      "a": "older",
      "b": "elder",
      "c": "an old",
      "d": "the old",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- The + adj ( the old = old people)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mary had enough time to go to France, but she had ___ money to go.",
      "a": "too few",
      "b": "too little",
      "c": "enough",
      "d": "enough of",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Too ... to VÂ \n- Little + uncountable nouns",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "You ___ to drop by my house any time you like.",
      "a": "are welcomed",
      "b": "welcome",
      "c": "are welcome",
      "d": "are welcoming",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- To be welcome to somebody or something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "There were ___ people watching the football game.",
      "a": "seven thousands",
      "b": "seven millions",
      "c": "thousands of",
      "d": "thousands",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Thousands of + plural noun: used when you are not giving an exact number\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The man is always complaining that he can't live on a ___ salary.",
      "a": "small",
      "b": "cheap",
      "c": "trivial",
      "d": "inexpensive",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- A small salary (opp: big salary)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}